lifeextension.com 2019-11-07

# Legal | Privacy Notice - Life Extension

REVISION Date: February 27, 2019

This website is owned and operated by Life Extension ("We"). LifeExtension.com ("Website") is committed to protecting your privacy. This Privacy Notice describes what information we collect, how we collect information, the steps we take to protect your information, and what we do with the information that we collect. By using the LifeExtension.com Website, you signify that you have read, understand, and agree to be bound by this Privacy Notice. We may change this Notice from time to time, and the changes are effective upon posting. Please review our Privacy Notice regularly. Your continued use of the Website after changes are posted constitutes your agreement to the changes. If you do not agree to the changes, please discontinue your use of the Website.

If you are using the Life Extension services while a resident in the European Union, European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland, this notice does not apply.  Please refer to the Life Extension GDPR Privacy Notice.

## Collection of Data

### Personal Information

We may collect and maintain any personal information you enter on our Website or provide to us in some other manner. For example, when you make a purchase from Life Extension or request a catalog, we collect and process different types of personal data for purposes of operating our business and providing our services.  Categories of data collected can include:

  * Basic personal details such as your name and job title;
  * Contact data such as your telephone number and postal or email address;
  * Financial data such as payment related information or bank account details;
  * Demographic data such as your address, preferences, or interests;
  * Website usage and other technical data such as details of your visits to our websites or information collected through cookies and other tracking technologies;
  * Customer data from third-party marketing partners that are combined with our customer data;
  * Recruitment related data such as your curriculum vitae, your education and employment history, details of professional memberships and other information relevant to potential recruitment to Life Extension;
  * Data that you may provide to us in the course of registering for and attending programs, events or meetings, including access and dietary requirements; and
  * Any other personal data relating to you that you may provide.

Please note that when you buy a blood test from Life Extension, your results will be sent to a third party for processing. Life Extension may use results from blood lab tests and/or clinical research studies for research, informational, and educational purposes from time to time. Any data used for these purposes will be anonymous, and we will not link blood test results with any specific individual.

### Non-Personally Identifiable Information

We may also collect certain non-personally identifiable information via the Website, such as Website usage activity and preferences, also known as profile or demographic data, the type of browser used by a visitor, the web page from which you came, and the operating system running the user's connections to the service. This data is not linked to you. This helps us make the Website as useful as possible.

The Website uses small files called "cookies," which are pieces of information that your browser receives from websites and stores on your computer's hard drive. For additional information regarding cookies, please see our Cookies Statement. By visiting our Website, you expressly agree to our collection and use of this data.

### What We Do With Data

The information we receive allows us to tailor our product offers and improve your shopping and browsing experience, making your experience easier and more enjoyable. It also enables us to process your purchases, confirm your orders, customize the content and layout of our pages, notify you about updates to our Website and products, and provide you with marketing information.

### How We Share Data

We may enter into relationships with different categories of third parties such as third-party service providers with affiliates, joint marketing partners, advertisers, or other companies that provide products or services that we believe may be of interest to you. In order to do so, we may share information like your name and postal address so you can receive the materials. We won’t disclose other information, such as your credit card account number, telephone number or email address. We just want you to continue to stay healthy and live better!

We may also disclose your information to third parties when we reasonably believe we are obligated to do so by law, and in order to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding suspected or actual prohibited activities, including without limitation, fraud, situations involving potential threats to the physical safety of any person, and violations of LifeExtension.com's Terms of Use. Finally, we may transfer information, including any personal information, to a successor entity in connection with a corporate merger, consolidation, sale of assets or other corporate change regarding our Website.

## Security

We recognize the importance of maintaining the security of your information. We have implemented technical, administrative, and physical security measures designed to protect your information from unauthorized access, disclosure, use, and modification. No security system is perfect and we cannot promise, and you should not expect, that your information will be secure in all circumstances.

## How We Respond to "Do-Not-Track" Signals

We may partner with ad networks and other ad-serving providers ("Advertising Providers") who serve ads on our behalf and others on non-affiliated sites. Some of those ads may be personalized, meaning that they are intended to be relevant to you based on information Advertising Providers collect about your visits to this Website and elsewhere over time. You may visit [www.aboutads.info](http://www.aboutads.info/) to learn more about this type of advertising and how to opt-out of this form of advertising by companies participating in the Digital Advertising Alliance ("DAA") self-regulatory program. Note that electing to opt out will not stop advertising from appearing in your browser or applications. It may make the ads you see less relevant to your interests. In addition, note that if you use a different browser or erase cookies from your browser, you may need to renew your opt-out choice.

## Children

The Life Extension Website is not directed to children under the age of 13, and we do not knowingly collect personal information from children under 13 years old.

## Foreign Users

Life Extension makes no claims that this Website is appropriate or may be accessed outside of the United States. Users from the European Union, European Economic Area, the United Kingdom, or Switzerland are advised not to disclose personal information on this Website. Access to the Website may not be legal by certain persons or in certain countries. If you access Life Extension's Website from outside the United States, you do so at your own risk.

## Third-Party Websites

Our Website may contain links to websites outside our control. This Privacy Policy does not cover any personal information that you provide to the owner of a third-party website, and we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these external websites. Please be aware that other websites operate under their own privacy policies and that these websites may collect your personal information. Thus, you should consult each website's privacy policy.

## Opt-Out

All Life Extension correspondences offer recipients a link to opt out of future mailings, or you may [click here](https://mycart.lifeextension.com/Account/ContactPreferences) to opt out. You may also choose to block all Life Extension emails, as well as postal mailings, by calling our Customer Service department at +1 855.874.9085 or by logging in to your account at LifeExtension.com.  However, if you opt out, we may still send you non-promotional emails, such as emails about your purchase or account, as well as promotional information contained in packages of products you order from us.

## Contact Us

If you have questions or comments regarding our privacy practices, please contact us here:

Information Security Officer  
3600 West Commercial Boulevard  
Fort Lauderdale, FL 33309 USA  
InformationSecurity@lifeextension.com

The Information Security Officer reports to Life Extension's General Counsel and is responsible for the content of this Privacy Notice.
